ritetag.com 2017-05-21

# RiteKit

RiteKit is the creator and publisher of the web pages available at RiteKit.com, RiteTag.com, RiteForge.com, Rite.ly and RitePush.com, ScrapeLogo.com and their Application Programming Interfaces (APIs), browser plugins, browser extensions and mobile applications, as well as the content within their on-site and off-site blogs, social media profile updates, content saved in content network profiles (e.g. Pinterest, Tumblr, List.ly, etc.), all linked pages in RiteKit sites, features, content, and applications. All above-noted entities are collectively referred to below as "RiteKit" and “Sites.”

## Extent of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers RiteKit’s treatment of personal information that we collect when you are on the Sites. This policy covers our treatment of any personal information that our business partners share with us.

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that RiteKit does not own or control, including but not limited to third party services you access through RiteKit, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage. We collect the following types of information from our users:

## Information Collected From Registered Visitors By Our Server

During the sign up we collect information necessary to provide the functions of RiteKit, RiteTag, RiteForge, RitePush, Rite.ly and ScrapeLogo:

### Email address

We send out occasional emails regarding major changes in the RiteKit website, browser plugins/extensions and mobile applications. The Settings pages in the Sites offers the option to opt out of these Informative emails.

We do not share your email address with third parties.

### Social network authorizations

To enable you to use the search and sharing features of RiteKit, we need you to authorize RiteKit to use your social network account(s). We will never share from your accounts without explicit action on your part.

## Recordings of your use of the Sites

We reserve the right to track of your use of the Sites. This is done for our internal study of how visitors, users and customers navigate the Sites so that we may learn how our user interfaces may be in need of clarity. Should your usage be evaluated, we will never automatically or manually store or associate with your name or IP address your search terms or research, Tag Set names or data, Tweets, posts or updates created or sent from RiteKit Sites or any other specific usage that might indicate anything about your interests. We will never access your web camera or in any way tie your likeness to any historical archive of your usage. We will never make information on your usage of the Sites available to anyone other than senior RiteKit staff. We will never provide information on your site usage to third parties, either for free or for compensation or in an exchange. 

## Information Collected From All Visitors By Our Server

Whenever you interact with the RiteKit website or applications, we may receive and store certain types of information. This information includes the data stored by the server in server logs, such as your IP address, RiteKit cookie information, and the information you request from the server. RiteKit may use this information to detect problems with the server, make changes so that the site is easier to use or create statistics. RiteKit may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.

## Information Collected From All Visitors via Google Analytics

If you visit this site and you have javascript enabled, your actions are tracked by Google Analytics. These Google services collect the following types of information:

  * Type of user agent (web browser) used, software manufacture and version number.
  * Type of operating system
  * Screen colors (color processing ability of the users screen)
  * Javascript support
  * Flash version
  * Screen resolution
  * Network location and IP address Can include country, city, state, region, county, or any other geographic data.
  * Hostname
  * Bandwidth (internet connection speed)
  * Time of visit
  * Pages visited
  * Time spent on each page of the website
  * Referring site statistics
  * The website (URI) the user came through in order to arrive at this website (example: clicking on a hyperlink from Yahoo.com that took the user to this website)
  * Search engine query used (example: typing in a phrase into a search engine like Google, and clicking on a link from that search engine)

This data is primarily used to optimize our website for our visitors. It's important to note that this data does not include any personalized identification information such as:

  * Names
  * Phone Numbers
  * Email Addresses
  * Mailing Addresses
  * Social Security Numbers
  * Bank Account Numbers
  * Credit Card Information

## Cookies

Cookies are simple pieces of information that we store on your hard drive through your Web browser. These cookies do not collect personal information.

Our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service are subject to change without notice.
